This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
However, the two could not escape Admiral Aka Inu,
and Ace died protecting Luffy.
Then suddenly, Blackbeard appeared, killing Whitebeard,
and accomplishing something truly unthinkable.
Just watch!
No, it can't be!
The Insatiable Aka Inu, Lava Fist's Pummel Luffy!
The H-C-U's coming down!
Run, Moran!
Abandon your bones!
We're all getting attacked!
Hey!
It's over.
There's nothing left.
The pirates.
They took everything we had.
Our citadel where we've watched over these waters for centuries.
It's all crumbling down.
The symbol of the Navy's strength.
This is a nightmare!
The...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Damn!
He planned this from the very start, didn't he?
He betrayed Whitebeard, captured Ace, and became a warlord!
All to force them into this battle!
All right then!
Take a good look!
Cause you ain't seen nothin' like this before!
They can't stop him now! No one can!
I can hardly blame them! I'd be crying too if my enemies had this kind of power!
Now what?
Took some time, but this is a hell of a payoff! I got the whole world wrapped around my finger!
You bastard!
Hey, what's wrong?
You don't want to fight? I'm right here!
If you let me get away, who knows what I might do!
Okay, I warned ya!
Now where to start?
Oh, I know!
How about I give Marineford a burial at sea?
He wouldn't dare!
Huh!
Sharkwave!
You can tear down our buildings, but in time we will rebuild them.
Huh!
But this island is different!
It's more than a symbol of our strength!
It stands in the center of the world!
Admiral!
And that means if we want to protect innocent people from criminals such as yourself,
it must be our stronghold, so its light can reach every corner!
Compassion is justice!
It defies chaos!
It doesn't perish!
And it will certainly not sink by your hand!
Turn to learn your place!
Well, that's a downright noble sentiment!
Compassion or what have you!
Well, come on!
Let's see what they're made of!
Agh!
That isn't good!
We gotta get this ship to the island quick!
Our men are gonna sink if we can't get them out of there!
Don't give up!
We'll leave it here together!
The ships are coming for us!
We can still make it!
Even if we have to strike our foes at the back, our victory must be absolute!
Pops wanted all of us to escape this place!
And that's what we're gonna do, dammit!
We'll strike the fear of justice into their hearts!
Crimes will be punished, and order will reign!
That's our duty!
As marines, he's right!
Come on, men! One last push!
Now's our chance!
We'll show every criminal what happens when you defy the law!
We'll let the whole world know!
That justice will prevail!
We made it!
In the name of justice!
Shizuru!
We bought you some time!
Get him out of here!
Good luck!
Oh no!
Bad move, Chipe!
Now get over here!
You're a pesky one, aren't you?
Either way, I'll finish this in time for dinner!
I'll strike you down here and now!
Newcoma Kenpo!
Aesthetic technique!
Laser surgery fist!
Ahh!
No! You melted my fabulous name!
Emporio Ivankov of the Revolutionary Army!
I'd heard your techniques were eccentric and that certainly seems to be the case!
Newcoma Kenpo!
Aesthetic technique!
This one's my fat suctioning fist!
I like it hot, baby!
Ahh!
This isn't a game, dammit!
Get the hell out of my way or pay the price!
Ahh!
Ah!
The ice is melting!
Ooh, that's not my face!
That's just my garish makeup!
Uh-oh!
Ahh!
Ah!
Fog, Nima, Go!
Who's next?
Don't let them escape!
Fire!
Oh, jeez.
I understand going after Blackbeard,
but this seems kind of like overkill.
I know they're pirates,
but haven't enough people been killed?
Hop them down!
Leave no man standing!
This is our chance!
Let's show the world what happens when they defy us!
What the...?
This is justice!
The power of the navy!
Destroy them!
What are these voices in my head?
Don't you dare, Akeidu!
You'd be wise to run while you can.
I have no business with you.
I dare not face him on dry land,
but the sea will aid me!
The water!
It's frozen solid!
Damn!
Akeidu!
Here he comes!
Nowhere left to run,
you bloated fish!
I'm helpless there.
Hand him over.
I'm putting an end to this!
This world will戦.
I don't know.
Long live!
Honey!
Now, while we're gone,
you cool and prestigious refrigerator.
This is not yours.
To be continued...
Still have some fight left in you? That's a pity.
Forgive me, Luffy. It seems that I couldn't uphold my vow.
You might have saved yourself instead of condemning the both of you.
If you keep making me miss, it won't be good for anyone.
A blow to the heart would be quick and painless.
Better than this.
The boy's got a hole in his chest. You sure you still want to protect him?
You know he's going to die either way.
Aaaaaah!
Jinbei. I know I might not make it out of this alive.
Jinbei. I'm sorry, but if I die, would you look after my brother for me?
Although your death was a tragedy, it did not sway my feelings.
Yet I found the answer to your request.
You aren't the only tenacious one here.
I've decided to protect this boy no matter the cause.
I refuse to let him perish.
Strike me as many times as you like.
I will shield him as long as I live.
What a load of crap.
He protected us.
Nabal!
Yeah!
They won't be up there long, so catch them when they fall and put them on a ship.
Uh-huh.
Why the sudden change of heart?
I say, if you're going to protect someone, then do it right.
I don't like either of you, but if you screw this up, then you'll let the Navy win.
Sorry, I blew it, guys.
You had so much faith in me, but I was nothing more than a coward all along.
I'll just float away somewhere and find a hole to crawl in,
because the only thing I'm the king of is to survive it.
Oh crap, they're getting away!
Fuck!
They're stuck in the air?
Wait, what's happening here?
Nice catch, Captain Buggy!
You saved Straw Hat and Jinbe!
I never should have doubted you.
He wasn't running.
He was just looking out for Straw Hat,
because all the glory in the world means nothing compared to the life of an old friend.
How beautiful!
His heart's as pure as a baby lamb!
I can't hear what they're saying, but I bet it's stupid.
Huh? Jinbe? And Straw Hat? What the hell?
What are you idiots doing all the way up here, and why are you both covered in blood?
This is weird, even for you guys.
Also, is it just me, or is it hot?
I don't know what's going on right now.
I'm afraid I allowed Luffy to be harmed.
Thank you, my red-nosed friend.
You saved our lives.
We're not friends. I don't even know what's going on right now.
I'm afraid I allowed Luffy to be harmed.
We must find a doctor. He was burned quite badly.
I don't care!
And good luck finding a doctor in the middle of this mess.
I had to trump the both of you right now.
Wait, were you making fun of my nose?
How many people do I have to go through to finish that breath?
Rose Rundle!
You're fools, each and every one of you.
Is one boy so damned important that you're willing to throw your lives away?
You may mock us if you please, but there is a strength in Straw Hat's tenacity that may prove invaluable to this world.
Pop spent his life on him. He has to carry on Ace's legacy.
This is the dawn of a new era, and we have a duty to see him through it.
Noble sentiment from a bunch of criminals, but in the end, it's just empty talk.
I won't hesitate to strike you down.
Same here.
Your insistence on killing Straw Hat just proves to us how much you fear him.
And if a tough guy like you is scared of a boy like him, that means he's worth protecting.
To the death if need be!
Ugh, can't you jackasses do anything without my help?
Hey, are you even listening to me?
You didn't just pass out, did you?
Hey, I didn't mean it, buddy. Don't die on me.
Come on, you gotta tell me where to go. I'm lost here.
Help!
Frankly, I should be applauding him for making Straw Hat suffer.
But I suppose the pirate in me would rather punch him in the face.
I see that trying to reason with you is a lost cause.
Have it your way!
This is too much!
It's Sengoku versus Blackbeard over there.
And it's Aga Inu versus the commanders on that side.
I thought this war was supposed to be over!
Captain Buggy, do something, anything!
I've got my hands full, okay?
Come on, guys, you're stressing me out over here.
Oh!
Captain!
We found a spot where the ice doesn't reach!
Then surface.
What is that?
It was underwater a ship it's a submarine
Another enemy is it?
That's a jolly roger
Huh, I don't take orders from you pal and besides what do you want with him anyway weirdo?
Actually, who the hell are you?
Straw hat may be my enemy someday, but I'll let the fates decide that one either way it'd be a waste to let him die here
Hand him over and we can escape he'll die without my help
Trust me. I'm a doctor
As senseless violence dies the battlefield red with blood
Luffy's allies struggle to save him as the Admirals maintain their assault with the world burning around him a boy
Who lacks the will to fight makes a stand that may change the future of the entire world on the next one piece?
The desperate scream courageous moments that will change the future
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
The new
So
It's